Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 5727
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- USPC/NALC - Yarmouth. (Box 16)
  - Whitman-Hanson Regional Schoool District 1139-1615-81, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Whittier Regional School and MTA AAA/Boston, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Yale University 2/9/81, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Yale University and Fed Em 35, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Yale University New Haven, CT Grievance 6/4/81, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Yale University, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Yarmouth and Government Employees AAA/Boston 1139-1574-79, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Greyhound and Amalgamated Transit Workers, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 28)